A Finding Aid to the LeRoy Neiman Papers, 1938-2005, in the Archives of American Art
Archives of American Art
Ali, Muhammad - see Ali vs. Frazier, 3.1: Lewis vs. Tyson 2002, .2.1: 2001, 3.1: GOAT (Greatest of All Time - A Tribute to Muhammad Ali) Book by Taschen, 2004, 3.2.1, 3.2.16, 4.1: 1964, 1965, 1966, 1967, 1970, 1971, 1974, 1976, 1977, 1978, 1980, 1985 1991, 1994, 1995, 1997, 1998, 1999, 2000, 2001, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 1960s, 4.2: The Ring Magazine as artist - 2.1: 1979, 4.1: 1966, 1967, 1970 ov, 1979
Muhammad Ali - Athlete of the Century, 2000 - 3.1: Muhammad Ali - Athlete of the Century, 2000-2002
Muhammad Ali - The Greatest Collector's Edition Magazine, 2002 - 4.1: 2002
Ali vs. Foreman, Zaire poster, 1974 - 4.1: 1974, 2000, 2002
Ali vs. Frazier
Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971 - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971
Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971, 1999 - 3.1: Holyfield -Lewis and Ali vs. Frazier I, 1999, 4.1: 2000
Ali vs. Frazier II etchings, 1974 - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971, 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier II, 1974, 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier III "The Thrilla in Manila," 1975, 4.1: 1990
Fight of the Century poster, 1971 - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier I, 1971
Thrilla in Manila poster, 1975 - 3.1: Ali vs. Frazier III "The Thrilla in Manila," 1975, 4.1: 2000
Ali vs. Holmes, 1980 - 3.1: Ali -Holmes 1980, 4.1: 2000
Ali vs. Spinks, 1978 - 3.1: Ali vs. Spinks 1978, 4.1: 2000
Bobrick - 4.1: 1977
Bowe, Riddick - 4.1: 1993, 1995, 1996, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Boxers Ball - 4.1: 1997
Boxing Beat Magazine - 4.1: 1988
Boxing Illustrated - 4.1: 1993
Boxing at the Ritz - 4.1: 1993
Boxing Writers Association of America - 1.1: Awards, 4.1: 1967, 1985, 2004
Brenner, Teddy - 2.1: 1978, 1979, 4.1: 1978, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Camacho, Hector - 4.1: 1986, 1997
Chavez, Julio Cesar - 4.1: 1993, 1996
Julio Cesar Chavez, pastel - 4.1: 1996
Julio Cesar Chavez, 1996 drawing - 4.1: 1996
Clay, Cassius - see Muhammad Ali
Coetzee - 4.1: 1984
Cooney, Gerry - see Holmes vs. Cooney, 2.1: 1989, 2000, 4.1: 1981, 1987, 2001, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
De La Hoya, Oscar - 3.1: The Fight of the Millennium, 1999, 3.1: De La Hoya vs. Vargas 2002, 3.1: De La Hoya vs. Hopkins 2004, 4.1: 1995, 1997
Oscar De La Hoya, 1995 - 4.1: 1997
De La Hoya vs. Mosely poster 2000 - 3.1: De La Hoya vs. Mosley 2000
De La Hoya vs. Whitaker, 1997 - 4.1: 1997
Dundee, Angelo - 3.1: Angelo Dundee Tribute 2002
Duran, Roberto - 3.1: Duran vs. Leonard I, II, III 1980 -1989, 4.1: 1980, 1983, 1984, 1994, 1995, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Ellis, Jimmy - 4.1: 1973 ov
F.I.S.T. - 2.1: 2000, 4.1: 2000, 2001
film, documentary - see Win a Few, Lose a Few, 1972
Foreman, George - see Ali vs. Foreman, 2.1: 1989, 4.1: undated, 1973, 1974, 1976, 1993, 1995, 1999, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Foreman Frazier Fight - 4.1: undated
Foreman vs. Holmes, 1999 - 4.1: 1999
Frazier, Joe - see Ali vs. Frazier, 2.1: 1975, 4.1: undated, 1969 ov, 1971, 1972, 1973, 1976, 1981, 1992, 1998, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Golden Gloves Championships - 4.1: 2000, 2001
Golota, Andrew - 4.1: 1996
Grant, Michael - see Lewis vs. Grant, 4.2: The Ring Magazine, 4.1: 2001
Graziano, Rocky - 4.1: 1990, 1991
HBO - 4.1: 2003, 2004
Hagler, Marvin - 3.1: Hagler vs. Hearns 1985, 4.1: 1984, 2000
Hearns, Thomas - 3.1: Hearns vs. Leonard 1981, 3.1: Hagler vs. Hearns 1985, 4.1: 2000, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Thomas Hearns, 1985 - 4.1: 1985
The Heavyweights, vinyl LP recording 1970 - 4.1: 1970, VII: Box 3
Heavyweight Collision - 4.1: 2003
Heavyweight Explosion, 2000 - 3.1: Heavyweight Explosion 2000
Hinds, Bobby - 2.2: Bobby Hinds 1990-2000
Holmes vs. Coetzee, 1984 - 4.1: 1984
Holmes vs. Cooney poster, 1982 - 3.1: Holmes vs. Cooney 1982, 4.1: 2000
Holmes, Larry - see Ali vs. Holmes, Holmes vs. Cooney, 3.1: Tribute to Joe Louis (Holmes vs. Spinks) 1981, 4.1: 1984, 1999, 2001, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Holmes vs. Cooney poster, 1982 - 3.1: Holmes vs. Cooney 1982, 4.1: 2000
Holmes vs. Shavers poster, 1979 - 4.1: 1979, 2000
Holmes vs. Spinks, 1985 poster - 4.1: 1985
Holyfield, Evander - see Tyson vs. Holyfield, 3.1: Holyfield-Lewis and Ali vs. Frazier I, 1999, 4.1: 1994, 1995, 1996, 2003
Hopkins, Bernard - Bernard Hopkins, 2004 - 3.1: De La Hoya vs. Hopkins 2004 Introduction of the Champions of the Ring, 1964-65 (or Ringside Madison Square Garden) - 4.1: 1965, 1983
Jones, Jr., Roy - 4.1: 1994, 1995, 1996, 2000; Roy Jones, Jr. - 4.1: 2000
King, Don - 4.1: 1977, 2003
Latin Legends - 4.1: 1992
Leonard, Sugar Ray - 3.1: Hearns vs. Leonard 1981, 3.1: Duran vs. Leonard I, II, III 1980-89, 4.1: 1980 ov, 1997, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Lewis, Lennox - see Lewis vs. Grant, 3.1: Holyfield -Lewis and Ali vs. Frazier I, 1999, 4.1: 1994, 1995, 2001
Lewis vs. Grant poster, 2000 - 4.1: 2000 and ov
Lewis vs. Tyson poster, 2002 - 3.1: Lewis vs. Tyson 2002
Liston, Sonny - 3.2.16, 4.1: 1964, 1965, 1974 ov, 4.2: Playboy Ephemera 1960s
Louis, Joe - 3.1: Tribute to Joe Louis (Holmes vs. Spinks fight) 1981
Joe Louis, 1983 - 3.1: Kayo Joe Louis Boxing Card 1991, 4.1: 1991
Malave, Chu Chu - 4.1: 1973
Mathis, Buster - 4.1: 1971
The Maulers 1993 lithograph - 4.1: 1993
Mayweather, Floyd - 4.1: 2000
McGirt, James "Buddy" - 3.1: McGirt vs. Whitaker 1993
Morrison, Tommy - 4.1: 1993, 1995
Mosely, Shane - see De La Hoya vs. Mosely
North American Boxing Federation - 4.1: 2000
Norton, Ken - 4.1: 1976, 1981, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
New Jersey Boxing Hall of Fame - 1.1: Awards - Inductions, 4.1: 2000
Olympic boxing - see Olympics
Patterson, Floyd - 4.1: 1972
Quarry, Jerry - 4.1: 1969 ov, 1970, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Red Boxers, 1973 - 4.1: 1973
Reid, David
David Reid, 1998 - 4.1: 1998
Ring Magazine - 3.2. Winners, 1983, Harry N. Abrams, 4.1: 1966, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Ringside and Training Principles, by Goodman and Homansky 2001 - 3.1: Ringside and Training Principles by Goodman and Homansky 2001
Robinson, Sugar Ray - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1989, 1994; Sugar Ray Robinson, 1969 - 4.1: 1969, 1998
Rocky - see Rocky films
Salute to Boxing Greats Award - 1.1: Awards
Shavers, Earnie - see Holmes vs. Shavers, 4.1: 1973 ov, 1977, 4.2: The Ring Magazine Spinks, Leon - see Ali vs. Spinks, 3.1: Tribute to Joe Louis (Holmes vs. Spinks) 1981, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Spinks, Michael - 3.1: Tyson vs. Spinks 1988, 4.1: 1987, 4.2: The Ring Magazine
Sting Like a Bee by Jose Torres and Bert Sugar - 2.1: 1972
Thornton, Wayne - 4.1: 1966
Toney, James - 4.1: 2003, James Toney, 1994 - 4.1: 2004
Torres, Jose - 4.1: 1966
Trinidad, Felix - 2.1: 1999, 3.1: The Fight of the Millennium, 1999
Tyson, Mike - 3.1: Mike Tyson portraits 1986-90s, 3.1: Tyson vs. Spinks 1988, 3.1: Lewis vs. Tyson 2002, 4.1: 1986, 1988, 1989, 1995, 1996, 1999 portraits - 4.2: The Ring Magazine, 4.1: 1999, 2001
Tyson vs. Holyfield, 1996 - 3.1: Tyson vs. Holyfield 1991-1996
Vargas, Fernando - 3.1: De La Hoya vs. Vargas 2002
Veteran Boxers Association of NY - 4.1: 1993
Whitaker, Pernell "Sweet Pea" - 2.1: 1999, 3.1: McGirt vs. Whitaker 1993, 4.1: 1993, 1995, 1997
Williams, Cleveland - 4.1: 1966, 1967
World Boxing Association Annual Awards Dinner - 4.1: 1994, 1995, 1996, 1997, 1998, 2000
World Boxing League - 4.1: Undated 2000s
Boy Scouts of America - 2.1: 1989, 4.1: 1989 ov
Boys' Athletic League - 4.1: 1974
Boys and Girls Clubs of America - 4.1: 1977, All Sports Hall of Fame Dinner - 4.1: undated 1970s, 1996, 1997, Legends & Fans Dinner - 4.1: 1990
Boys Town of Italy - 4.1: 1987, 1988, 1992
Bradley, Bill - 3.1: Bill Bradley 1978 -2000, 3.1: Women's Basketball Hall of Fame, 1993, 3.2. LeRoy Neiman: An American in Paris, 1994, 4.1: 1981, 1999
Branca, Ralph - 3.1: The Shot Heard 'Round the World, 1991, 2.1: 1994, 4.1: 1994
Brayton, Scott - see auto racing
Brazil Stock Exchange, 1985 - 2.1: 1985
Brenner, Teddy - see boxing
Brett, George - 4.1: 1990; George Brett, 1992 - 4.1: 1992
Brice, Bobbie - 4.1: 1982
Bride's Magazine - 3.1: Early Fashion Illustration 1949-57
Broadway - see musicals or Times Square, 2001
Brooklyn Bridge, 1995 - 1.1: Honorary Degrees - Saint Francis College, 3.1: Brooklyn Bridge, 1995, 4.1: 1995, 1998
brothel - see Mustang Ranch
Brown, Jim - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-73
Brown, Larry
Larry Brown - 4.1: 1972
Bruce, Lenny - 4.1: 1976
Jeffrey Bryan Fine Art - 4.1: 1989
Bryant, Coach Paul "Bear," Coach Bear Bryant, 1979 - 2.1: 1979, 1983, 1989, 4.1: 1981
Budweiser - see Anheuser-Busch
Buena Vista Bar - 4.2: Bartender Magazine 1987-1992
bull riding - see rodeo
bullfight - 4.1: 1960
Kneeling Matador, 1968 - 2.1: 1976
El Matador, 1965 - 2.1: 1986
Matador, 1967 - 4.1: 1989
La Plaza de Toros - 4.2: Playboy 1961, see Appendix E
Toreador, 1968 - 4.1: 1984
Burgdorff Cultural Center - 4.1: 1999
Burger King - see promotions
Burns, George - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993
Burr & Associates (Cameron Burr) - 2.1: 1992, 1993, 3.1: The Texas Longhorns, 1985, 3.1: '21' Club, 1990 (photo)
Bush, President George H.W. and Barbara - 1.1: Honorary Degrees c., 2.1: 1989
Bush, President George W. - 2.1: 2003
Bushkin, Joe - 4.1: 1997
Busker Alley - 3.1: "Busker Alley," 1995
Byrams, Gina - 3.1: Hammer Galleries Solo Exhibition 1970
Byrne, Janet - see Neiman, Janet
C
CBS Sports television - 2.1: 1979, 2.2: CBS Sports, 4.1: 1978, 1985
CD ROM - VII
Caesar's Palace - see casinos
Cahill, Very Reverend Joseph - 1.1: Honorary Degrees, St. John's University, Honorary Doctorate, 1980, St. John's University, Gold Medal of Honor, 1985
Caine, Michael - 2.1: 1981
Calder, Alexander - 4.1: 1973 (see exhibitions, two-person)
calendars - 4.1: 1974 ov, 1976, 3.1: Wild Animals and Art of Sport Calendars 1992-94 and ov, 3.1: Golf Courses Calendar 1996
California Cuisine (The Lark Creek Inn), 198? - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 4.1: 2004
Call of the Wild, by Jack London - 3.1: Call of the Wild 1993
Camacho, Hector - see boxing
Camp David Peace Accords, 1998 - see Carter, President Jimmy
Campbell, Earl - 2.1: 1982
Campbell's Soup - 4.1: 2004
Cannes Film Festival - 3.1: Beauty, the Beach, and the Bizarre 1984
Cape Town, South Africa - 4.1: 1997
Capone, Al, Al Capone - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 4.1: 1972, 1992, 1995
Cappy Productions - 2.1: 2000
Caracas, Venezuela - 2.1: 1972, 1976, 1977, 1980, see exhibitions: Museo de Bellas Artes
"Caring is Fashionable" - 4.1: 1981
Carlson, Bill - see "Neiman's Cuba"
Carnaval, 1981 - 3.2.6, 3.2 ov., see Haskell, Nikki
Carousel, 1958 - 4.1: 1950s
The Carousel of Hope - see also Appendix A, 3.1: Carousel Ball 1982-present
Carpenter, Rob - 4.1: 1982
carpet - see tapestry
Carreras, Jose - 3.1: The Three Tenors, 1996
cars - see automobiles
Carter, Don - see bowling
Carter, Lillian - 3.1: Peace Treaty, 1980, V: 1970s
Carter, President Jimmy - 4.1: 1978, 1989
Peace Treaty, 1980 - 3.1: Peace Treaty, 1980
Camp David Peace Accords, 1998 - 4.1: 1998
Casey at the Bat, by Ernest L. Thayer, illustrated by LeRoy Neiman - 3.2.13
casinos and gambling - 3.1: Circle Gallery 1972, 4.1: 1984, 1997, 1998, see also The Art of Gaming Through the Ages
Baden Baden, 1988 - 4.1: 1988
Bally's Park Place, Atlantic City - 2.1: 1999
Bally's, Las Vegas - 2.1: 1999
Le Casino de Monte Carlo, 1969 - 4.1: 1984
Caesar's Palace, Las Vegas - 2.1: 1998, 3.1: Caesar's Palace 1980, 3.1: Alan King Caesar's Palace Tennis Classic 1980-83, 3.1: Caesar's Palace Grand Prix 1981-83, 3.1: Holmes-Cooney 1982, 4.1: undated 1970s, 1976, 1979, undated 1980s, 1980, 1981, 1982, 1985, 1987, 1993
Desert Inn - 2.1: 1983, 1984, 1997, 1998, 4.1: 1998
Les Femmes du Caesar's Palace - 4.1: undated 1980s
Chemin de Fer, 1966 (1991 serigraph release) - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection touring exhibition 1989, 4.1: 1991, 1998
Craps Kinshasa - 4.1: 1976
Fiesta Casino Hotel - 2.1: 1997
Gambling Times Magazine - 4.1: 1984
Gaming Table, 1958 - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection touring exhibition 1989
The Golden Nugget, Las Vegas - 3.1: Golden Nugget Casino, Las Vegas 1988
Green Table, 1972 - 4.1: undated, 1984
Harrah's Trump Plaza, Atlantic City - see Trump, Donald
High Stakes, 1974 - 4.1: 1984
The Hustler - see The Hustler
International Poker, 2004 serigraph of earlier painting - 4.1: 2004
Merv Griffin's Resorts Casino and Hotel, Atlantic City - 3.1: Merv Griffin's Resorts Casino Exhibition 1990
Ocean Club, Atlantic City - see promotions
The Poker Game - 4.1: 1980
Rio Suite Hotel and Casino, Las Vegas - 2.1: 1997
Roulette, 1957 - 4.1: 1950s
Roulette, 1970 - 2.1: 1970, 4.1: 1995
Roulette II, 1996 serigraph - 3.2:11, 4.1: 1996, 1997
Sands Hotel and Casino, Las Vegas - 2.1: 1994, 1997
Slots-change Girl, 1980 - 4.1: 1984
Stud Poker - 4.1: 1984
Tropicana Resort & Casino, Las Vegas - 2.1: 1999, VII: Artifacts
Casino Legends Hall of Fame, LeRoy Neiman Award - 2.1: 1999, 4.1: 1999
Folies Bergere - 3.1: Folies Bergere, Tropicana 1983, 3.1: Folies Bergere Neiman Chips 1999, 4.1: 1999
t.v. commercial - 4.1: 1984
Trump Plaza, Atlantic City - see Trump, Donald
Trump Taj Mahal, Atlantic City - see Trump, Donald
Vegas Blackjack - 4.1: 1984, 1996
catalogue raisonnes - 3.2.5, 3.2.9, 3.2.14
Cavett, Dick - 2.1: 1999
"Celebration 2000" Exhibition - 3.2.14
Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993 - 3.1: Celebrity Night at Spago, 1993
Centaur Galleries, Las Vegas - see exhibitions
Center Art Galleries, Hawaii - 3.1: Center Art Galleries Exhibition, Hawaii 1985, 4.1: 1984, 1987
Central Park Boathouse - see restaurants
cereal box - see Wheaties
Chabot Galleries - 2.1: 1989
Chamberlain, Wilt - see 3.1: Basketball Superstars, 1975 -76, 3.1: Kareem Abdul -Jabbar, 1984, 3.1: Wilt Chamberlain 2000, 4.1: 1981
champagne - 3.1: Duval LeRoy Champagne 1999-2001
Champagne Taittinger - 3.1: 1993
Champagne...Uncorked! by Rosemary Zraly - 3.1: Saks Fifth Avenue 1994-1999, 3.1: Champagne...Uncorked! by Rosemary Zraly 1996
Champions vs. MS - 2.1: 1977
Champs-Elysses
Le Champs- Elysses, 1992 - 4.1: 1996
The Champs-Elysees, la Voie Triomphale, 1994 - 4.1: 1997
Chandler, Charlotte - 3.1: Charlotte Chandler 1978-84, 3.1: March of Dimes' Gourmet Gala 1985
Channel Thirteen, New York - 2.1: 1984, 4.1: 1983
Charismatic - 4.1: 1999
charity - 2.1: Charities (all files), see also AIMS (Committee to Aid Multiple Sclerosis), American Cancer Society, American Diabetes Association, American Heart Association, Association for the Help of Retarded Children (AHRC), Boys & Girls Clubs of America, Boys Town of Italy, Carousel of Hope (Children's Diabetes Foundation), Champions vs. MS, Children's Hearing Institute, Citymeals-on-Wheels, Concern's Charity of Champions, Cystic Fibrosis Foundation, Doodle for Hunger, Good Tidings Foundation, Hope House Ministries, Hospital Relief Fund of the Caribbean, International Heart Foundation, International Sephardic Education Foundation, Jackie Robinson Foundation (under Robinson, Jackie), Jimmy Fund, Juvenile Diabetes Foundation, Leukemia Society of America, Make-a-Wish Foundation, Monmouth Park Charity Ball, Muscular Dystrophy Association, Myasthenia Gravis Foundation, National Multiple Sclerosis Society, North Shore Child and Family Guidance Association, Race to Erase MS, Rock for the Cure, Ronald McDonald House, Special Olympics, United Cerebral Palsy Association, United Way, 4.1: 1981, 1992, 1999; see also animals: rescue
Charlie Cosmetics - see promotions
Chavez, Julio Cesar - see boxing
chef - 3.1: James Beard 1985-87, see also Bennett, Chef John; Clark, Chef Patrick; Kopf, Stefan; Lomonaco, Chef Michael; food; restaurants; Soltner, Chef Andre
Chemical Bank - 2.2: Manufacturers Hanover and Chemical Bank, VII: Box 3
Cher - 4.1: 1981
chess - see Fischer, Bobby
Chicago Board of Trade, 1974-75 - 2.1: 1977, 1989, 4.1: 1977
Chicago Public Library - 4.1: 1955-59
Chicago Serigraphic Workshop - 2.1: 1977
children, artwork by - 2.2: Artwork from Children
children, letters from - 2.2: Mrs. Vladimir's Class 1975-85, 2.2: Hutchinson KS, Elementary Schools, 1976-78, 2.2: Mr. Silver's Class 1978-81, see also various letters in 2.1 Fan Mail files
Children at Heart - 4.1: 1996
Childrens Diabetes Foundation - 3.1: Carousel Ball 1982-present
Children's Hearing Institute - 4.1: 1994
China - 2.1: 1983
Chinaglia, Georgio - see soccer
Choate School - 4.1: 1969
Christie's - 4.1: 1978
Christina Galice Gallery - 2.1: 1990
churches - 4.1: 1964, 1965; The Organ at St. Paul the Apostle, 1965 - 4.1: 1965
cigars - 2.1: 1997, 1998, 4.1: 1996, 1997, 1998
Cigar Aficionado Magazine - 2.1: 1995, 4.1: 1995, 1997
Components of Fire by (Aaron Sigmond or Jim Mauro) with Foreword by LeRoy Neiman - 2.1: 1997
Playboy's LeRoy Neiman Selection by Don Diego - 3.1: Playboy's LeRoy Neiman Selection by Don Diego, 1997
Puro Cigar Company - see Sigmond, Aaron
Rhythm and Smoke Cigar Video - 3.1: Rhythm and Smoke Cigar Industry Video 1997-1998
Wine, Women and Cigar, 1996 - 3.1: Playboy's LeRoy Neiman Selection Cigars 1996, 4.1: 1999, 4.2: Bartender Magazine Cincotti, Peter - 4.1: 2002 ov.
Circle Galleries, Chicago and New York - 2.1: 1979, 1989, 4.1: 1973, 1981, 1989, 1.2: Felicie Correspondence, see exhibitions, solo: Circle Galleries and "Ali-Frazier"
Circus, 2000 - 3.1: Circus 2000, 4.1: 2001
Cirker - Hayes Warehouse - IID: Inventory of Prints Stored in Warehouse 1970s-80s
Cities in Schools - 3.1: Cities in Schools and Harlem Streets, 1981, 4.2: Arts Magazine
City by the Bay, 1993 - see San Francisco
City By The Bay, by Charles Fracchia, cover illustration by LeRoy Neiman - 3.1: San Francisco Series 1991-93
Citymeals-on-Wheels - see Beard, James
Clark, Chef Patrick Dean - 4.1: 1998
Classic Leather - see promotions
Classic Moments Watches - 3.1: Classic Moments LeRoy Neiman Watch Collection 1989
Classico Postcards - 2.1: 1992
Claude-Jobrack, Madeleine - 3.1: '21' Club, 1990 (photo)
Clay, Cassius - see boxing: Ali, Muhammad
Clayton, Derek - 3.1: New York City Marathon 1984-2001
Clemens, Roger, The Rocket - Roger Clemens, 2003 - 3.1: The Rocket - Roger Clemens, 2003
Clemente, Roberto - 4.1: 1992, Roberto Clemente - 4.1: 1973
Clinton, President Bill - 3.2. Big Time Golf, 1992, 4.1: 1992
clothing - VII
clothing stores - see Marshall Fields, Neiman Marcus, Pallack, Rick, and Saks Fifth Avenue, 4.1: 1958
Clough, Charles - 4.1: 1986
Club El Morocco - 4.1: 1979
Clubhouse Turn, 1975 - see horse racing
Coalition for the Homeless - 4.1: 1986
Coca-Cola Company - 2.1: 1994
Coetzee - see boxing
Coghlan, Eamon - see running
Cohen, Mouli - 3.1: Soft Paintings 1989
collectibles - see promotions
collectors - 4.1: 1969, 1980, 1981, see Wolfson
college sports - see basketball, football
Columbia Space Shuttle - 4.1: Undated ov
Columbia University - School of the Arts - 3.1: LeRoy Neiman Center for Print Studies, Columbia University 1995-present; School of General Studies - 2.1: 1977
Comaneci, Nadia - see gymnastics
Comedia dell' Arte - 3.1: Royal Doulton collectible plates 1974-78
comic strips - see Doonesbury
commercials - see Promotions
Commodities Magazine - see The Chicago Board of Trade, 1974-75
Concern Foundation
Concern's Charity of Champions - 4.1: 1983
conductors - see Bernstein, Leonard; Slatkin, Leonard
Contemporary University - 4.1: 1980
Cooney, Gerry - see boxing
computer art - 4.1: 1975
Conner, Bart - see gymnastics
Converse - 2.1: 1982
Bill Corum Award - 1.1: Awards
Corvette, Limited Edition Neiman - 3.1: Corvette 1984, V: 1980s, Rendezvous a la Corvette, 1984 - 3.1: Corvette 1984
Cosby, Bill - 4.1: 1991, 1997
Cosell, Howard - 4.1: 1987, 1995, V: 1991
cosmetics - see promotions
Cotton Club - 4.1: undated
Countdown to Superbowl, by Dave Anderson - 3.1: Countdown to Superbowl by Dave Anderson 1969
Country Rambler Magazine - 2.1: 1976, 4.1: 1976 ov
Couples - 4.1: 1976
Cow Parade, NYC - 3.1: Cow Parade NYC, 2000
cowboys - see The Lone Ranger, National Cowboy Hall of Fame, rodeo
Creative Communications - 2.1: 1976
cricket - 4.1: 1961
Crosby, Bing - 3.1: 43rd Crosby National Pro-Am, 1984
crossword puzzles - 4.1: 1990, 1991, 1995, 1998, 1999
Crozier, William - V: 1995
Csonka, Larry - 4.1: 1973, 1974; Larry Csonka - 4.1: 1972
Cuba - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman in Cuba" Solo Exhibition, Pratt Institute, New York, 2003, 4.1: 1979
Cuban Dancers, 1997 - 3.1: Rhythm and Smoke Cigar Video 1997-98
The Culinary Arts exhibition - 3.1: The Culinary Arts exhibition 1998
Culinary Institute of America - 4.1: 2000
Cunningham, Merce - see dance
Current Biography - 4.1: 1996
Curtis, Mike - 3.1: Gridiron Football News 1971-1973
Curtis, Tony - 2.1: 1988
cycling
3.1: Tour de Trump
Boul Mich Bike Rally, 1978 - 2.1: 1983, 4.1: 1978 ov
Indoor Cycling - 4.1: 2000, 2002
Tour de France - 4.1: 1984
Cystic Fibrosis Foundation - 4.1: 1996
D
Daily Double - see Fran Joswick Therapeutic Riding Center
Dalai Lama - 2.1: 2003
Daley, Robert - 4.1: 1966
Daley, Mayor Richard - 4.1: 1968
Dali, Salvador - 4.1: 1977, 1986, 1991, 2002 (mentioned throughout 1980s and 1990s)
Dan's Papers - 2.1: 1998, 1999, 4.1: 1997 ov
dance - see also ballet
Cunningham, Merce
Merce Cunningham Studio - 4.1: 2004
"Fringe TOMAR 2000" Festival Internacional de Danca Contemporanea, 2000 - VII
Graham, Martha - 2.1: 1989
Jacki Sorenson, 1981 - 4.1: 1981
Davidson Gallery - 4.1: 1986
Davis, Marvin and Barbara - 2.1: 1985, 3.1: Carousel Ball 1982-present
Davis, Jr., Sammy - 3.1: Frank Sinatra at Royal Albert Hall 1989, 4.1: 1964, 1981, 1982, 1984, 1991, V: early 1960s, Bojangles, 1984 - 4.1: 1986
Dawkins, Peter - 2.1: 1980, 3.1: Peter Dawkins Poster 1988
De la Hoya, Oscar - see boxing
De La Vega, James - 4.1: 1999
Dean Day Gallery - 2.1: 1982, 1983, 1989, see also exhibitions
Dear Muffo, by Harold Conrad - 4.1: 1982
Edward J. DeBartolo Corporation - 2.2: DeBartolo Corporation and Associated Institutions 1989-91
DeBusschere, Dave - 4.1: 1974
The Dedication - 4.1: 1969
Deer Path Art League - 4.1: 1950s
Defiant, 1987 - see sculpture
Degregorio, Ernie - 2.1: 1976
Dekker, Mary - V: 1980s
Del Coronado Petit Galop, 1976 - 4.1: 1976
Del Greco, Maria -2.3: Letters from Artists, 4.1: undated, 1996
Delacroix's Tiger - see animals
Delligatti, Ralph - 4.1: 1992
Denver, CO - see auto racing
Denver, John - 4.1: 1994
Derek, Bo and John - 2.1: 1998, 4.1: 1985
Des Moines, Iowa
Des Moines Ballet - 3.1: Des Moines Ballet Commissions 1983-1986
Des Moines Symphony - 4.1: 1979
Desert Inn, Las Vegas - see casinos: Caesar's
Desert Symphony - see music: classical
designers - 4.1: 1997
Dewar's - 4.1: 1971
Dial-A-Dinner - 4.1: 1994
Diamond, Neil - 4.1: 1984
El Diario la Prensa - 2.1: 1987
A Dictionary of Sporting Artists, by Mary Ann Wingfield - 4.1: 1992
Dill, Bob - 2.1: 1997, 1999
Diller, Phyllis - 2.1: 1995, 1996, 1999
DiMaggio, Joe - 4.1: 1992
Joe DiMaggio: Yankee Clipper, 1998 - 3.1: Joe DiMaggio 1998-1999, 4.1:1998 Joe DiMaggio: Study for "Yankee Clipper", 1998 - 3.1: Joe DiMaggio 1998-1999
DiPietro, Marylou - 2.1: 1979, 3.2.3
diving - see swimming and diving
Dixon, Rod - see running
dog - see animals
Dokes, Michael - 4.1: 1993
Domingo, Placido - 3.1: The Three Tenors, 1996
Doodle for Hunger - 3.1: Doodle for Hunger I, II, III, IV, V, 2000-2004
Doonesbury - 4.1: 1981
Door County - 3.1: "LeRoy Neiman - A Retrospective Exhibition of Works on Paper," Fairfield Gallery, 2001
Dorfman, Fred - see Fred Dorfman, Inc.
Dorset, Tony - 2.1: 1982
Doubletake Gallery - 4.1: 1999
Douglas, Kirk, Kirk Douglas, 1984 - 2.1: 1999, 3.1: National Cowboy Hall of Fame 1985
dreams - 3.1: Folies Bergere, Tropicana, Las Vegas 1983
Drinhaus, Helmut - 2.2: Helmut Drinhaus 1988-2000
Driscoll, John (President of Iona College) - 1.1: Honorary Degrees, Iona College, Honorary Doctorate, 1985
Dubai - 2.1: 1988
Dublin Bar "The Stag's Head" - see The Stag's Head Bar, 1961
Dufresne, Isabelle - 4.1: 1988
Duguay, Ron - 4.1: 1982
Dundee, Angelo - see boxing
Duneier, Clyde - 4.1: 1993
Dupont, Andre - 4.1: 1974
Dupont pens - see promotions
Duran, Roberto - see boxing
Durocher, Leo - 3.1: Leo Durocher 1974-94, 3.1: Phil Rizzuto 1994, 4.1: 1968, Leo Durocher - 3.1: Leo Durocher 1974-94
Duval LeRoy, Carol - 3.1: Duval LeRoy Champagne, 1999
Dyansen Gallery - 3.1: Dyansen Gallery Playboy Collection touring exhibition 1989, 4.1: 1990, 1991, 1992, 1996, 1997
Van Dyke, Dick - 3.1: Emerald Art Gallery Solo Exhibition, Coronado, CA 1976
Dylan, Bob, Bob Dylan, 2001 - 4.1: 2001
E